So I click on write it for me and I just say that I want to have a long detailed article
mentioning every single point out there when it comes to getting together the perfect
CV/Resume, right? And I wait so it says gotcha uh nope nope I don't want you to do that
over here. I want you to generate it in my document the very left side of this page.
And I wait during detailed article for you document the left side I need to access the
current document state which will be just open the document so I can what are you talking
about. So yeah this is my document, right? And what else? So it will not automatically
it seems like it will not automatically do it for me but what I can do is that I can use
it to generate the text over here and I can copy it and bring it over here. So okay
I can you know worries do it over here then. Just do it over here then. And I give it
a command and I wait. Hyper-write limit hit. Okay perfect now we need to upgrade to
premium and pay something per month for premium ultra or genius.